[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hannah means grace and charm.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This famous Italian was the author of many novels, which were later turned into highly successful movies, such as The Sicilian and The Godfather trilogy.", "correct_answer": "Mario Puzo", "incorrect_answers": ["Frank Messina", "Michele Pane", "Paul Gallico"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what childrens novel, written by L. Frank Baum, did the Cowardly Lion make his first appearance?", "correct_answer": "The Wonderful Wizard of Oz", "incorrect_answers": ["Peter Pan in Kensington Gardens", "The Lion, The Witch and the Wardrobe", "Alice in Wonderland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In every country in the world, except one, moving the head up and down means yes and moving the head side-to-side means no. In what one nation is that not the case?", "correct_answer": "Bulgaria", "incorrect_answers": ["Romania", "Kurdistan", "Hungary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to statistics, which of the following people is most likely to commit suicide?", "correct_answer": "A middle-aged divorced man.", "incorrect_answers": ["A recovering alcoholic.", "A middle-aged divorced woman living alone.", "A teenage boy who smokes marijuana."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although natural, this food contains more calories than beet-sugar. It is used in a lot of skin-care products, but in the ancient Egyptians considered it --to be a cure for impotence and sterility.", "correct_answer": "Honey", "incorrect_answers": ["Chocolate", "Avocado", "Cinnamon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Over 10,000 squibs were used in the film The Wild Bunch. What is a squib?", "correct_answer": "A simulated bullet hit.", "incorrect_answers": ["An old film technique in which animation is mixed with real people.", "A film technique in which a few  vehicles  look like a long line of  vehicles.", "A  method of over dubbing the audio of a scene to make it appear as if many people are talking."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Most animals and plants are not able to synthesize vitamin C by themselves.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There was a sequel to the 80s action comedy 48 Hrs..", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1984 blockbuster hit Ghostbusters, what was Rays last name?", "correct_answer": "Stantz", "incorrect_answers": ["Spengler", "Barrett", "Venkman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the scale created by an entomologist who had been stung by almost every type of bee, ant, and wasp?", "correct_answer": "Schmidt Sting Pain Scale", "incorrect_answers": ["Kardashev Sting Pain Scale", "Shwan Sting Pain Scale", "Ludwig Sting Pain Scale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did JB and KG stop to eat in the movie Tenacious D, while they were on their way to the Rock  Roll History Museum?", "correct_answer": "The Halfway House Cafe", "incorrect_answers": ["The Blackheart Cafe", "The Random House Diner", "The Herron Diner"]}]